uvrx.com 2017-12-31

# Privacy Policy for www.uvrx.com

Privacy Policy for www.uvrx.com

The privacy of visitors to www.uvrx.com is important to us.

At www.uvrx.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use/visit this site, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files includes your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Opera, Firefox etc), date/time stamp and screen resolution. This information helps us determine the best design/layout to use for maximum compatibility with our visitors.  
IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
We use third party advertisements to help support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on www.uvrx.com, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites) to personalize the advertising content that you see.

DoubleClick DART cookies  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements).   
This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about fishing, you may see fishing reel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about Football).   
DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does **NOT** track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.   
You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to·not having this information used by these companies, [click here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

You can disable or selectively turn off cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with some websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. A good option is to scan your computer for "bad" cookies using "spybot search and destroy"  
Turning off or disabling cookies should not affect your experience at www.uvrx.com
